oi guys!
who are?
oh,
beauty bro,
Cayon!
Po,
stand here!
ha ha. all good?
And there?
all Massa!
pleasure, pleasure!
tamo walking
OR live here for a walk
you believe that people
Are you more stressed nowadays?
yes OR no?
obvious yes.
he works at the institute he created
1 box of happiness.
and believe it or not,
inside this box
there's something that will change your day for the better.
can i show?
I love Brigadier!
,
the box I make,
we make to sell to travel the world
six Passengers with the Tibelga
there are ten generations,
I exchange for you,
EU amei
that's 1 pineapple joke so go
Space in the World,
boot there I'm not pregnant
It's because I don't have Internet.
ok, thanks people!
thank you!